Do you feel that way?
そんな気がするんですか?
I'll do something even more embarrassing.
もっと恥ずかしいことするんですよ
You want me to include this, you stiff dick.
これ入れて欲しいでしょ、ガチガチのチンチン
There are some Lanky gels coming out.
何個かランキージェルが出てる
This is how it turned out.
こうなっちゃってますよ、これ
Did you want it that much?
そんなに欲しかったんですか?
I'll put this in, this.
これ入れてあげます、これ
What do you think?
どうです?
I'll put it in there properly.
ちゃんとこっかまで入れてあげますね
Because it's dangerous, it's tightening more and more,
だってやばい、どんどん締め付けるけど、
this.
これ
It's weird just the way it is.
そのままだっておかしいんだね
One more time.
もう一回
No, I'm sorry.
いや、すいません
Hey, I just can't resist this cuteness.
ちょっと、こんな可愛くて我慢できなくて
Sorry to bother you.
お邪魔しました